Finding Aid for Sesquicentennial Office (University of Michigan) records, 1959-1967
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs: Sesquicentennial events and office staff. Phil Davis Sesquicentennial Exhibition
  - Photographs
    - Contact prints, photos taken for exhibition, 28 folders
      - R.F. experiment, physics: Forester in tree. Physics student assembling copper ring coil., 178; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Dr. Vonbaumparten with sea slugs. August [Physics Machine Shop]. Prisoners Dilemma. Goldfish. [?] choir chamber., 179; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Monkey, bearing research-N.G. Dr. Sam Barnes, Army lecture. Construction. Girls' orientation group, 180; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Guitarist and girl friend. M. M. Brown at Hill organ (3 are 56mm), 181; 15 frames (Box 13)
      - Pretzel Bell, 182; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - [not received], 183 (Box 13)
      - W. A. running shots, 184; 30 frames (Box 13)
      - Interlochen counselors ed. Shell rehearsal. Rain. Junior violinist, 185; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Interlochen orchestra rehearsal. Photographer in bowl, 186; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Interlochen 2475-Shell rehearsal-Kresge, 187; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Interlochen-concert and awards in Bowl N.G. (56mm), 188; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Interlochen-Band bowl rehearsal-behind bass, horns (56mm), 189; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Interlochen-pre-rehearsal in Kresge-tuning tympani (56mm), 190; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Interlochen students, general, 191; 34 frames (Box 13)
      - Interlochen pre-rehearsal and instrument repairman (56m-), 192; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Maynard Klein, 193; 32 frames (Box 13)
      - Interloch,7~n-viola lesson, tent theater, 194; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Interlochen dancers.-Rehearsal in bowl, 195; 30 frames (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails-speech therapist in woods; kids looking at Hasselblad (56mm), 196; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails outdoor counseling (56mm), 197; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Speech Camp-little kids, outdoor therapy; also older kids through trees, 198; 34 frames (Box 13)
      - Speech counseling in woods and on beach through trees (56mm), 199; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Speech camp-round robin and mail, 200; 40 frames (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails-speech therapist on beach; boy speaking at lectern in woods, 201; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Speech Camp-mail; announcements; cabin practice for round robin, 202; 35 frames (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails-counseling in woods, on beach and checker game (56mm), 203; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Speech Camp-baseball, waterfront, checker game (56mm), 204; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails-fishing and swimming, 205; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails-fishing. Forestry-saw filing, 206; 34 frames (Box 13)
      - Forestry-soil check; log rolling, match splitting, 207; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Forestry-Tool room; burling, 208; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Forestry -- classroom; tool room; burling (56mm), 209; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Forestry-store-office (56mm), 210; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Forestry Camp-Store and mess hall, 211; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Forestry Camp-Classroom, evening. Also geology classroom, Jim McClurg, 212; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Forestry Camp-Mensuration Woods, 213; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Forestry Measurement; office. Geology, 214; 35 frames (Box 13)
      - Geology Mapping field trip-plus X, 215; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - [Geology]-Steg and Marty; Jim McClurg in classroom, 216; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Geology-Ike Smith and kids checking aerial maps-, 217; 34 frames (Box 13)
      - Geology-Mapping, Ike Smith; campfire (56mm), 218; 11 frames (Box 13)
      - Camp Davis from mountain (56mm), 219; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Geology-Surveyors on mountain (56mm), 220; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Geology-Bill Kelly and kids, field trip. Also Jim McClurg, 221; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Geology-Campfire; Lucy in kitchen; dining hall, 222; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Geology -- Stege[?], Lucy and preparation for mapping trip. Also Bill Kelly and rock samples, 223; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Bill Kelly-gold panning, 224; 38 frames (Box 13)
      - Geology-dining hall, Lucy. [Paleontology]-Hibbard and student in camp, 225; 33 frames (Box 13)
      - Dr. Hibbard and grad student at site., 226; 38 frames (Box 13)
      - Hibbard and grad student at site (56mm), 227; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Mt. Evans-1st roll Dr. Lawrence Jones (56mm), 228; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - On top of Mt. Evans 2nd roll (56mm), 229; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Kim (56mm) 3, 230 (Box 13)
      - Leslie White (56nm), 231-232; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Leslie White; Manupelli [George -- art professor?], 233; 18 frames (Box 13)
      - Losh, 234-235; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Stanley Quartet, Rackham. Students registering in Greene House, 236; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Student registering in dorm. Football practice, 237; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Greene House-2475-Students entering, 238; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Signing in East Quad. Football practice, 239; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - East Quad and registration [moving in], 240; 33 frames (Box 13)
      - Coming in-East Quad, 241; 34 frames (Box 13)
      - Vocational Therapy-shoe maker., 242; 38 frames (Box 13)
      - Occupational Therapy. East Quad, 243; 35 frames (Box 13)
      - Jim Hurt, football. Appliances, 244; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Registration-paper on ground, and in Waterman, 245; 38 frames (Box 13)
      - Registration-telephoto shots (56mm), 246; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Registration-looking down on fluorescent lights (56mm), 247; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Registration; girls sitting on floor (56mm), 248; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Registration-Plus X, 249; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Band marching to pep rally, and rally at Rackham, 250; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Pep rally and sing, Rackham 2475, 251; 33 frames (Box 13)
      - Book buying. Sam. Window. History plaque, 252; 23 frames (Box 13)
      - Nurses, window shots, 253; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Nurses-nothing roll, 254; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Swimming and gymnastics, 255-256; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Gymnastics, 257; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Nurses. Gym parallel bars, 258; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Jim Hunt [head trainer-taping a knee], 259; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Football practice. Baseball telephoto, 260; 35 frames (Box 13)
      - Football and baseball, Hasselblad (56mm), 261; 16 frames (Box 13)
      - Football practice-500mm lens (56mm), 262; 16 frames (Box 13)
      - Sport parachute, motorcycle, Eccentrics, sailing club, 263; 30 frames (Box 13)
      - Marching Band practice. Nurses, 264; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Football team dressing, 265; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Football-pre-game warmup -- Revelli [band director], 266; 38 frames (Box 13)
      - Band formation on field. Players standing at bench, 267; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Bandsmen and coaches at bench, 268; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Band and crowd at football game, 269; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Nurses-nutrition. Super Wide lens (56mm), 270; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Nurses-class in nutrition. Rollei (56mm), 271; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Nurses-tasting. Rollei (56mm), 272; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - TV studio. Music School building (56mm), 273; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Baroque Trio (56mm), 274; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Baroque Trio (56mm) 8, 275 (Box 13)
      - Baroque Trio. Daily editors. (56mm), 276; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Pep rally (56mm), 277; 16 frames (Box 13)
      - Football-running players, blurred (56mm), 278; 16 frames (Box 13)
      - Building Homecoming displays 2475, 279; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Hatcher tea-flash Leica, 280; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Hatcher tea-Nikon, 281; 36 frames (Box 13)
      - Galens, campus in snow, 282; 22 frames (Box 13)
      - Galens, near Hill Auditorium (56mm), 283; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Galens sign at crossing (56wn), 284; 12 frames (Box 13)
      - Galens sign, no. 2 (56mm), 285; 12 frames (Box 13)
- Negatives
  - Exhibition negatives (Box 14)
    (negatives arranged by number corresponding to contact sheet number.)
    Restricted: Staff use only